Guide to the Washington State University Office of the President: Charles Clement French Records 1957-1966
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- 1963
  - Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 426)
  - S, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 427)
  - Sabbatical leaves, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 428)
  - Safety building, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 429)
  - Sanitarian, University, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 430)
  - Scholarship and development fund, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 431)
  - Scholarships, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 432)
  - Sciences and Arts, College of: Kennedy, T. H., 1963
    - Kennedy, T. H., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 433)
    - Ray, B. Roger, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 434)
    - Thompson, A. W., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 435)
  - Seattle -- First National Bank, Seattle, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 436)
  - Secretarial Studies, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 437)
  - Sigma Xi, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 438)
  - Sociology and Anthropology, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 439)
  - Speech, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 440)
  - Speeches, Articles, Excerpts, etc., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 441)
  - Staff Personnel office, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 442)
  - Staff Personnel office
    - Civil Service Employee's Advisory Committee, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 443)
    - Personnel committee, Board of Regents, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 444)
  - State
    - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 445)
    - Auditor, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 446)
    - Census board, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 447)
    - Central budget agency, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 448-449)
    - Civil defense, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 450)
    - Education, Board of, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 451)
    - General Administration, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 452)
    - Governor, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 453)
    - Health, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 454)
    - Legislature, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 455)
    - Legislature: Interim committee on education, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 456)
    - Legislature: Legislative budget committee, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 457)
    - Legislative council, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 458)
    - Liquor control board, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 459)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 460)
    - Museum, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 461)
    - Natural Resources, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 462)
    - Public Instruction, Superintendent of, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 463)
    - Senators and Representatives, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 464)
    - Treasurer, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 465)
  - Streit, Selma A., Deceased, Estate of, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 466)
  - Student Counseling Center, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 467)
  - Student Health Service, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 468)
  - Students Book Company, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 469)
  - Summer session, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 470)
  - T, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 471)
  - Technology, Institute of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 472)
  - Tech. Building: Engineering addition, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 473)
  - U, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 474)
  - United States
    - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 475)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 476)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Richland and Hanford), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 477)
    - Civil defense, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 478)
    - Defense, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 479)
    - Defense, Dept. of:
      - Air Force, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 480)
      - Air Force advisory panel, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 481)
      - Army, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 482)
      - Army ROTC panel, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 483)
      - Navy, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 484)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 485)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, Dept. of (Research grants), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 486)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 487)
    - Interior, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 488)
    - Interior, Dept. of (BPA advisory council), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 489)
    - International Development, Agency for, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 490)
    - National Academy of Sciences (National Research Council), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 491)
    - National Science Foundation, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 492)
    - National Science Foundation (proposals), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 493)
    - Senators Representatives, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 494)
    - Veterans Administration, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 495)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 496)
    - Treasury Dept., 1963 (Box 12, Folder 497)
  - Universities and Colleges
    - California, University of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 498)
    - Central Washington State College, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 499)
    - Eastern Washington State College, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 500)
    - Gongaza University, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 501)
    - Idaho, University of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 502)
    - Michigan, University of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 503)
    - Miscellaneous, A-L, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 504)
    - Miscellaneous, M-Z, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 505)
    - Oregon, University of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 506)
    - Oregon State University, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 507)
    - Washington, University of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 508)
    - Washington State institutions (5), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 509)
    - Washington State University, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 510)
    - Western Washington State College, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 511)
  - V, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 512)
  - Veterinary Medicine, College of, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 513)
  - W, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 514-515)
  - Washington Congress of Parents Teachers, Inc., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 516)
  - Water Resources Center, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 517)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 518)
  - X-Y-Z, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 519)
  - YMCA YWCA, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 520)
  - YMCA YWCA: Senior-faculty weekend, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 521)
- 1964
  - A, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 522)
  - Administrations, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 523)
  - Admissions: Junior colleges, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 524)
  - Advisory boards, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 525)
  - Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 526)
  - Agricultural experiment stations, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 527)
  - Agricultural experiment stations
    - Irrigation, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 528)
    - Northwestern Washington, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 529)
    - Tree fruit, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 530)
    - Western Washington, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 531)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 532)
  - Agricultural Extension Service: 4-H club, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 533)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Institute of, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 534)
  - Agriculture, College of, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 535)
  - Agronomy, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 536)
  - Am, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 537)
  - American Assembly, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 538)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 539)
  - American Association of University Women, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 540)
  - American Council on Education, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 541)
  - Animal Sciences, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 542)
  - Applications, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 543)
  - Architect, University, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 544)
  - Architect, University space analyst, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 545)
  - Architectural Engineering, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 546)
  - ASWSU, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 547)
  - Athletic Association of Western Universities, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 548)
  - Audio Visual Center, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 549)
  - B, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 550)
  - Botany, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 551)
  - Budget office, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 552)
  - Building names, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 553)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 554)
  - Business Administration, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 555)
  - Business Manager, Office of, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 556)
  - Business Manager, Office of: Vending machines, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 557)
  - C, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 558)
  - Chamber of Commerce, miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 559)
  - Chemistry, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 560)
  - Civil Engineering, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 561)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 562)
  - Committees
    - Academic program, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 563)
    - Academic standing, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 564)
    - Budget, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 565)
    - Catalog subcommittee of EPC, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 566)
    - Commencement, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 567)
    - Distinguished alumnus award, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 568)
    - Educational policies, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 569)
    - Faculty executive, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 570)
    - Freshmen - faculty weekend, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 571)
    - Graduate studies, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 572)
    - Health and safety, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 573)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 574-575)
    - Patent, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 576)
    - Research, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 577)
    - Space priorities, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 578)
    - Ten-year planning, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 579)
    - Traffic control, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 580)
  - Communications, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 581)
  - Complaints, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 582)
  - Compton Union, Wilson, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 583)
  - Comptroller, Office of, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 584)
  - Computing Center, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 585)
  - Consolidated endowment fund, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 586)
  - Cougar clubs, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 587)
  - D, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 588)
  - Data Processing, Office of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 589)
  - Dean of Students, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 590)
  - Dean of the Faculty, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 591)
  - Dean of the Faculty
    - Academic report, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 592)
    - Grade studies, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 593)
    - Improvement of instruction, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 594)
    - Institutional research, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 595)
    - Invited lectures (WSU faculty), 1964 (Box 15, Folder 596)
    - Small classes, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 597)
    - Teaching load studies, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 598)
  - Deans, directors, department chairmen, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 599)
  - Dormitories for men, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 600)
  - E, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 601)
  - Economics business research, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 602)
  - Economics, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 603)
  - Economics Business, College of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 604)
  - Education, College of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 605)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 606)
  - Education building, Alfred A. Cleveland, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 607)
  - Electrical Engineering, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 608)
  - Electron microscope, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 609)
  - Engineering, College of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 610)
  - English, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 611)
  - Entomology, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 612)
  - F, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 613)
  - Faculty, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 614)
  - Financial information
    - Cost studies, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 615)
    - Salary schedules, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 616)
    - Tuition and fees, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 617)
  - Fine Arts, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 618)
  - Food Science, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 619)
  - Football
    - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 620)
    - WSU -- Stanford, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 621)
    - WSU vs Oregon State University, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 622)
    - WSU vs University of the Pacific, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 623)
    - WSU vs University of Wyoming, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 624)
  - Foreign Languages, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 625)
  - Forestry Range Management, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 626)
  - G, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 627)
  - General Education Curriculum Advisory Program, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 628)
  - General Extension Service, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 629)
  - General reserve, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 630)
  - Genetics, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 631)
  - Geology, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 632)
  - Governing boards, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 633)
  - Graduate Records, Office of, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 634)
  - Graduate School, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 635-636)
  - H, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 637)
  - High school summer camp, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 638)
  - History, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 639)
  - Home Economics, College of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 640)
  - Honors program, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 641)
  - Horticulture, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 642)
  - House Food Service, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 643-644)
  - I, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 645)
  - Industrial Research, Division of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 646)
  - Industrial Research, Division of Grant County Research Center, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 647)
  - Information, Office of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 648)
  - Information Science, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 649)
  - Intercollegiate athletics, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 650)
  - International Student Office, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 651)
  - J, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 652)
  - Journalism, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 653)
  - K, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 654)
  - KWSC: Radio and Television, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 655)
  - L, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 656)
  - Land acquisitions, leases, etc., 1964 (Box 16, Folder 657)
  - Land-grant Association (The Association of State Universities Land-grant Colleges), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 658)
  - Library, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 659)
  - Library, Friends of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 660)
  - M, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 661)
  - Mathematics, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 662)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 663)
  - Metallurgy, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 664)
  - Military Coordinator, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 665)
  - Military Coordinator: Air Science, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 666)
  - Military Coordinator: Military Science, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 667)
  - Music, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 668)
  - N, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 669)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association, The, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 670)
  - National Commission on Accrediting, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 671)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 672)
  - National Education Association, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 673)
  - Neill, Marshall A., 1964 (Box 16, Folder 674)
  - Northwest Association of Secondary High Schools, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 675)
  - Nuclear reactor, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 676)
  - O, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 677)
  - P, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 678)
  - Pacific Science Center Foundation Committee, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 679)
  - Pakistan, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 680)
  - Pharmacy, College of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 681)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 682)
  - Physical Education for Men, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 683)
  - Physical Education of Women, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 684)
  - Physics, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 685)
  - Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 686)
  - Placement Bureau, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 687)
  - Political Science, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 688)
  - Political Science Administration, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 689)
  - President's office, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 690)
  - Property inventory, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 691)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 692)
  - Publications, Office of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 693)
  - Publications, Office of WSU news bulletin, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 694)
  - Publications building, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 695)
  - Purchasing office, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 696)
  - Q, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 697)
  - R, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 698)
  - Recommendations, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 699)
  - Regents, Board of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 700)
  - Registrar, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 701)
  - Registrar - enrollment, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 702)
  - Reservations, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 703)
  - Resident instructional staff, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 704)
  - Retirement Insurance Office, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 705)
  - Retirements, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 706)
  - Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 707)
  - S, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 708)
  - Sabbatical leaves, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 709)
  - Scholarship, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 710)
  - Scholarship development fund, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 711)
  - Sciences and Arts, College of
    - Kennedy, T. H., 1964 (Box 17, Folder 712)
    - Ray, B. Roger, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 713)
    - Thompson, A. W., 1964 (Box 17, Folder 714)
  - Seattle-First National Bank, Seattle, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 715)
  - Secretarial Studies, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 716)
  - Service garage, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 717)
  - Sigma Xi, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 718)
  - Sociology Anthropology, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 719)
  - Speech, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 720)
  - Staff Personnel Office, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 721)
  - Staff Personnel Office
    - Civil Service Employee's Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 722)
    - Personnel committee of the Board of Regents, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 723)
  - State
    - Agricultural, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 724)
    - Attorney General, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 725)
    - Auditor, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 726)
    - Census Board, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 727)
    - Central Budget Agency, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 728)
    - Civil defense, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 729)
    - Conservation, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 730)
    - Economic Opportunity Act, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 731)
    - Education, Board of, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 732)
    - General Administration, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 733)
    - Governor, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 734)
    - Governor (Higher Education Facilities Commission), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 735)
    - Health, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 736)
    - Health, Dept. of (State Advisory Council on Nuclear and Radiation), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 737)
    - Legislature, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 738)
    - Legislature (Interim committee on education), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 739)
    - Legislative council, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 740)
    - Liquor Control Board, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 741)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 742)
    - Natural Resources, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 743)
    - Public Instruction, Superintendent of, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 744)
    - Public Pension Commission, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 745)
    - Racing Commission, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 746)
    - Research Council, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 747)
    - Senators and Representatives, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 748)
  - Student Book Store, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 749)
  - Student Counseling Center, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 750)
  - Summer session, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 751-752)
  - T, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 753)
  - Technology, Institute of, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 754)
  - U, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 755)
  - U.S.
    - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 756)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 757)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Richland and Hanford), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 758)
    - Defense, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 759)
    - Defense, Dept. of
      - Air Force, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 760)
      - Air Force Advisory panel, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 761)
      - Army, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 762)
      - Army ROTC panel, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 763)
      - Navy, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 764)
      - ROTC advisory panel, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 765)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 766)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (Research grants), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 767)
    - Housing and Home Finance agency, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 768)
    - Interior, Dept. of, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 769)
    - Interior, Dept. of (BPA advisory council), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 770)
    - International Development, Agency for, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 771)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 772)
    - National Academy of Sciences (National Research Council), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 773)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 774)
    - National Science Foundation, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 775)
    - National Science Foundation (Consultant services), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 776)
    - National Science Foundation (Proposals), 1964 (Box 18, Folder 777)
    - Senators and Representatives, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 778)
    - Treasury Dept., 1964 (Box 19, Folder 779)
  - Veterans Administration, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 780)
  - Universities and Colleges
    - California, University of, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 781)
    - Central Washington State College, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 782)
    - Eastern Washington State College, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 783)
    - Gonzaga University, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 784)
    - Idaho, University of, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 785)
    - Miscellaneous, A-L, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 786)
    - Miscellaneous, M-Z, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 787)
    - Oregon, University of, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 788)
    - Oregon State University, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 789)
    - Washington, University of, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 790)
    - Washington State Institutions (5), 1964 (Box 19, Folder 791-793)
    - Washington State University, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 794)
    - Western Washington State College, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 795)
  - V, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 796)
  - Veterinary Medicine, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 797)
  - W, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 798)
  - Washington College Association, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 799)
  - Washington Education Association, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 800)
  - Washington State Grange, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 801)
  - Water research, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 802)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 803)
  - Whitman County, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 804)
  - Wildlife research unit, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 805)
  - YMCA and YWCA, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 806)
- 1965
  - A, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 807)
  - Administrative Council, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 808)
  - Admissions, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 809)
  - Admissions: Community colleges, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 810)
  - Advisory Boards, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 811)
  - Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 812)
  - Agricultural Experiment Stations
    - Coastal Washington, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 813)
    - Irrigation, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 814)
    - Office of Director, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 815)
    - Northwestern Washington, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 816)
    - Tree fruit, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 817)
    - Western Washington, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 818)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 819)
  - Agricultural Extension Service: 4-H clubs, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 820)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Institute of, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 821)
  - Agriculture, College of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 822)
  - Agronomy, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 823)
  - American Assembly, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 824)
  - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Educ. (AACTE),1965 (Box 20, Folder 825)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 826)
  - American Association of University Women, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 827)
  - American Council on Education, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 828)
  - American Heritage Association, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 829)
  - Animal Sciences, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 830)
  - Applications, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 831)
  - Architect, University, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 832)
  - Architect, University: Space analyst, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 833)
  - Architecture, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 834)
  - ASWSU, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 835)
  - Athletic Association of Western Universities, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 836)
  - Audio-visual Center, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 837)
  - B, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 838)
  - Bacteriology and Public Health, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 839)
  - Botany, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 840)
  - Budget office, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 841)
  - Building names, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 842)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 843)
  - Business Administration, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 844)
  - C, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 845)
  - Camp Easter Seal, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 846)
  - Chemistry, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 847)
  - Civil Engineering, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 848)
  - Committees
    - Academic standing, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 850)
    - Board of trustees, Memorial Hospital, Inc., 1965 (Box 20, Folder 851)
    - Commencement, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 852)
    - Committee on committees, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 853)
    - Educational policies, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 854)
    - Health and Safety, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 855)
    - Lecture-artist series, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 856)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 857)
    - Patent, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 858)